

651.399.2589 | sean09lee@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/sean09lee | www.seandlee.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE



Driven young professional new to San Diego with a broad technical skill set. Experienced developer in agile process work flows and quality software development to implement client visions for new and existing web sites. Thrives in competitive environments that constantly embrace new technologies.

Skills include:

User Interface Design / Testing, Debugging, & Documentation / User Training and Support / Agile Development / Sitecore Certified

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business, 2013

University of Minnesota, Carlson School of Management

Majors: MIS, Finance

Collegiate Affiliations: Delta Sigma Pi

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming/Web: C#, VB.NET, JavaScript, CSS, LESS, SASS, HTML

Software: Visual Studio, TFS, PLSQL, Jenkins, Git

Database/DBMS: Oracle, SQL

EXTRACURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

- General Mills Recruiting Committee
- General Mills Code Camp Committee
- General Mills Intern Committee
- Reading Buddies Community Service

WORK EXPERIENCE

GENERAL MILLS, 2013 - Present

Experienced Application Developer, 2014 - Present

- Utilize Knockout JS, C#, .Net, and Sitecore CMS to maintain and enhance GMI web components and core sites such as www.bettycrocker.com and www.boxtops4education.com
- Create and update technical documentation for process flow and system snapshots while working as part of an agile team of 20+ developers
- Utilize Dynatrace, Coradiant, SCOM, and Jenkins to monitor, build, and deploy code in line with GMI software quality standards
- Upgrade major .Net Retail Trade applications to reduce technical debt for holistic margin management savings upwards of \$5 Million per year
- Technical Skills: C#, MVC, .NET 4.5, SQL, WCF, REST, SOA, Knockout, jQuery, HTML5, LESS

Application Developer I, 2013 - 2014

- VB.Net and PLSQL development to maintain and enhance the internal Retail Trade click-once application to handle upwards of \$1 billion in transactional invoices and savings deals
- Oracle development to maintain and enhance the Retail Trade Reporting application
- Lead front-end user experience and .Net MVC web development for Planning Calendar web application
- Technical Skills: MVC, VB.NET (2.0, 4.0, and 4.5), PLSQL, WCF, REST, SOA, jQuery, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap

SPARKSTARTER, 2014 – 2015

Consulting Developer, June 2015 - Sept 2015

- Provide technical direction and on-boarding for junior developers
- Provide technical consultation on code and UI/UX reviews
- Work as part of an agile team to provide direction in redesigning the mobile app
- Technical Skills: AngularJS, jQuery, PHP, MySQL, REST, SOA, HTML5, SASS, Ionic

Application Developer, 2014 - June 2015

- Develop landing web page and web version of app at www.sparkstarter.com using JQuery and
- Develop initial version of mobile app using AngularJS, PHP, and MySQL back-end
- Technical Skills: AngularJS, jQuery, PHP, MySQL, REST, SOA, HTML5, SASS, Ionic